Meet me at the Randy's Donut
by the airport at 2:00 a.m.
(Sheldon:)What is that you're eating?
(Sheldon:)Tonight is pizza night.
(Leonard:)I'd like to refer that
to my attorney.
(Priya:)According to what I see here,
(Priya:)Thursday nights
are Franconi's pizza night.
(Sheldon:)Yes, and when Franconi's
went out of business,
(Sheldon:)we switched to Graziano's.
(Howard:)That's interesting.
(Howard:)Can you just switch
restaurants like that, Priya?
(Priya:)A good question, Howard.
(Priya:)Turns out you can't.
(Sheldon:)According to
the document
(Priya:)you drew up, Sheldon,
the selection
(Priya:)of a new takeout restaurant
requires public hearings
(Priya:)and a 60-day comment period.
(Priya:)Were those criteria met?
(Sheldon:)No.
Opa! Opa!
Opa!